Fear. Treachery. Bloodlust.
Thousands of years ago,
these were the forces that ruled our world.
A world where prey were scared of predators.
And predators had an uncontrollable,
biological urge...
to maim, and maul, and...
Blood! Blood! Blood!
And death.
Back then, the world was divided in two.
Vicious predator...
or meek prey.
But over time, we evolved.
And moved beyond our primitive, savage ways.
Now, predator and prey live in harmony.
And every young mammal has
multitudinous opportunities.
Yeah.
I don't have to cower in a herd anymore.
Instead, I can be an astronaut.
I don't have to be a lonely hunter anymore.
Today, I can hunt for tax exemptions.
I'm gonna be an actuary!
And I can make the world a better place.
I am going to be...
a police officer!
Bunny cop? That is the most
stupidest thing I ever heard.
It may seem impossible to small minds...
I'm looking at you, Gideon Grey.
But, just 211 miles away...
stands the great city of Zootopia!
Where our ancestors
first joined together in peace...
and declared that anyone can be anything!
Thank you and good night!
Judy, you ever wonder how your mom
and me got to be so darn happy?
Nope.
Well, we gave up on our dreams
and we settled. Right, Bon?
Oh, yes, that's right, Stu.
We settled hard.
See, that's the beauty of complacency, Jude.
If you don't try anything new,
you'll never fail.
I like trying actually.
What you father means, hon...
is it's gonna be difficult,
impossible even,
for you to become a police officer.
Right. There's never been a bunny cop.
Bunnies don't do that.
- Never.
Then, I guess I'll have to be the first one.
Because I am gonna make the world
a better place.
Or, heck, you know, you want to talk
about making the world a better place...
no better way to do it than
becoming a carrot farmer.
Yes! Your dad, me...
your 275 brothers and sisters.
We're changing the world!
One carrot at a time.
Amen to that.
Carrot farming is a noble profession.
Just putting the seeds in the ground.
At one with the soil.
Just getting covered in dirt.
You get it, honey.
It's great to have dreams.
Yeah. Just as long as you don't
believe in them too much.
Where'd the heck she go?
Give me your tickets right now...
or I'm gonna kick your meek little sheep butt.
Cut it out, Gideon!
What are you gonna do? Cry?
Hey!
You heard her. Cut it out.
Nice costume, loser.
What crazy world are you living in
where you think a bunny could be a cop?
Kindly return my friend's tickets.
Come and get them.
But watch out, because I'm a fox,
and like you said
in your dumb little stage play...
us predators used to eat prey.
And that killer instinct
is still in our "Dunnah."
I'm pretty much sure
it's pronounced "DNA."
Don't tell me what I know, Travis.
You don't scare me, Gideon.
- You scared now?
- Look at her nose twitch!
She is scared!
Cry little baby bunny.
Cry, Cry...
You don't know when to quit, do you?
I want you to remember this moment...
the next time you think you will ever
be anything more than just a stupid...
carrot-farming, dumb bunny.
That looks bad.
Are you okay, Judy?
Yeah. I'm okay.
Here you go.
Wow! You got our tickets!
You're awesome, Judy!
Yeah, that Gideon Grey doesn't
know what he's talking about.
Well, he was right about one thing.
I don't know when to quit.
Listen up, cadets.
Zootopia has 12 unique ecosystems
within its city limits.
Tundratown...
Sahara Square...
Rainforest District, to name a few.
You're gonna have to master all of them
before you hit the streets, or guess what?
You'll be dead!
Scorching sandstorm!
You're dead, Bunny Bumpkin!
1,000-foot fall!
You're dead, Carrot Face!
Frigid ice wall!
You're dead, Farm Girl!
Enormous criminal.
You're dead.
Dead, dead, dead!
Filthy toilet! You're dead, Fluff Butt.
Just quit and go home, fuzzy bunny!
There's never been a bunny cop.
- Never.
Just a stupid,
carrot-farming dumb bunny.
As mayor of Zootopia,
I am proud to announce...
that my Mammal Inclusion Initiative
has produced...
its first police academy graduate.
Valedictorian of her class,
ZPD's very first rabbit officer...
Judy Hopps.
Oh, gosh.
Assistant Mayor Bellwether, her badge.
- Oh, yes. Right!
- Thank you.
Yay, Judy!
Judy...
it is my great privilege
to officially assign you...
to the heart of Zootopia: Precinct One.
City Center.
Congratulations, Officer Hopps.
I won't let you down. This has been
my dream since I was a kid.
It's a real proud day for us little guys.
Bellwether, make room, will you?
Come on.
Okay, Officer Hopps.
Let's see those teeth!
- Officer Hopps, right here!
- Look this way please!
Hold still. Smile!
We're real proud of you, Judy.
Yeah. Scared, too.
Really, it's kind of
a proud-scared combo.
I mean, Zootopia. So far away.
Such a big city.
Guys...
I've been working for this my whole life.
We know. And we're just
a little excited for you, but terrified.
The only thing we have to fear is fear itself.
And also bears.
We have bears to fear, too.
Say nothing of lions and wolves.
- Wolves?
- Weasels.
You play cribbage with a weasel.
And he cheats like there's no tomorrow.
You know what, pretty much all
predators. And Zootopia's full of them.
Oh, Stu.
And foxes are the worst.
Actually, your father does have
a point there. It's in their biology.
Remember what happened with Gideon Grey?
When I was nine.
Gideon Grey was a jerk
who happened to be a fox.
I know plenty of bunnies who are jerks.
Sure, we all do. Absolutely.
But just in case...
we made you a little care package
to take with you.
- And I put some snacks in there.
- This is fox deterrent.
Yeah, that's safe, to have that.
This is fox repellent.
The deterrent and the repellent,
that's all she needs.
- Check this out!
- For goodness sake.
She has no need for a fox Taser, Stu.
Come on. When is there not
a need for a fox Taser?
Okay, look! I will take this,
to make you stop talking.
Terrific! Everyone wins!
Arriving, Zootopia Express.
Okay, gotta go! Bye!
Bye, Judy!
I love you guys.
Love you, too.
Oh, cripes, here come the waterworks.
Oh, Stu, pull it together.
Bye, everybody!
- Bye-bye, Judy!
- Bye, Judy!
I love you!
Bye! Bye!
Good bye!
I messed up tonight
I lost another fight
Lost to myself
But I 'll just start again
I keep falling down
I keep on hitting the ground
But I always get up now
To see what's next
Birds don't just fly
They fall down and get up
Nobody learns without getting it wrong
I won't give up
No I won't give in
Till I reach the end
And then I'll start again
No I won't leave
I want to try everything
I want to try even though I could fail
I won't give up
No, I won't give in
Till I reach the end
Then I'll start again
No, I won't leave
I want to try everything
I want to try even though I could fail
Try everything
I'll keep on making those new mistakes
And I'll keep on making them every day
Those new mistakes
Try everything
I'm Gazelle. Welcome to Zootopia.
Welcome to the Grand Pangolin Arms.
Luxury apartments with charm.
Complimentary delousing
once a month. Don't lose your key.
Thank you.
Hi! I'm Judy, your new neighbor.
Yeah? Well, we're loud.
Don't expect us to apologize for it.
Greasy walls.
Hey, shut up!
Rickety bed.
- You shut up!
Will you shut up?
Crazy neighbors.
I said, "Shut up!"
I love it!
Shut your mouth, shut up.
Come on!
He bared his teeth first!
Excuse me.
Down here.
Hi.
O-M-Goodness!
They really did hire a bunny! What!
I gotta tell you, you are even cuter
than I thought you'd be!
You probably didn't know, but a bunny
can call another bunny "cute"...
but when other animals do it...
it's a little...
I am so sorry!
Me, Benjamin Clawhauser...
the guy everyone thinks is just a flabby,
donut-loving cop, stereotyping you.
No, it's okay. Oh, you've actually got...
There's a...
In your neck. The fold.
Where? Oh!
There you went, you little dickens!
I should get to roll call, which way do I...?
Bullpen's over there to the left.
Great. Thank you.
That poor little bunny's
gonna get eaten alive.
Hey, Officer Hopps.
You ready to make the world a better place?
Atten-hut!
All right! Everybody sit.
I've got three items on the docket.
First... we need to acknowledge
the elephant in the room.
Francine...
Happy birthday.
Number two.
There are some new recruits
with us I should introduce...
but I'm not going to...
because I don't care.
Finally, we have 14 missing mammal cases.
All predators, from a giant polar bear
to a teensy little otter.
And City Hall
is right up my tail to find them.
This is priority number one.
Assignments.
Officers Grizzoli...
Fangmeyer, Delgato.
Your teams take missing mammals
from the Rainforest District.
Officers McHorn, Rhinowitz, Wolfard.
Your teams take Sahara Square.
Officers Higgins, Snarlov, Trunkaby.
Tundratown.
And finally, our first bunny...
Officer Hopps.
Parking Duty.
Dismissed.
Parking duty?
Chief!
Chief Bogo?
Sir, you said there were
14 missing mammal cases.
- So?
- So, I can handle one.
You probably forgot, but I was
top of my class at the Academy.
Didn't forget. Just don't care.
Sir, I'm not just some token bunny.
Well, then writing 100 tickets a day
should be easy.
100 tickets.
I'm not gonna write 100 tickets.
I'm gonna write 200 tickets.
Before noon.
Boom!
200 tickets before noon!
201.
Hey, watch where you're going, fox!
Where'd he go?
I don't know what you're doing
skulking around during daylight hours...
but I don't want any trouble in here.
So, hit the road.
I'm not looking for any trouble either, sir.
I simply want to buy a Jumbo Pop...
for my little boy.
You want the red or the blue, pal?
I'm such a...
Come on, kid. Back up.
Listen, buddy. What? There aren't any
fox ice cream joints...
in your part of town?
No, no. There are.
There are. It's just, my boy,
this goofy little stinker...
he loves all things elephant.
Wants to be one when he grows up.
Is that adorable?
Who the heck am I to crush
his little dreams? Right?
You probably can't read, fox,
but the sign says...
"We reserve the right to refuse service...
"...to anyone."
So, beat it.
You're holding up the line.
Hello? Excuse me.
You're gonna have to wait your turn
like everyone else, meter maid.
Actually, I'm an officer.
Just had a quick question.
Are your customers aware
they're getting snot and mucus...
with their cookies and cream?
What are you talking about?
I don't want to cause you any trouble,
but I believe scooping ice cream...
with an ungloved trunk
is a Class 3 health code violation.
Which is kind of a big deal.
Of course,
I could let you off with a warning...
if you were to glove those trunks and,
I don't know...
finish selling this nice dad and his son a...
What was it?
A Jumbo Pop.
Please.
$15.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Oh, no. Are you kidding me?
I don't have my wallet.
I'd lose my head if it weren't attached
to my neck. That's the truth.
Oh, boy. I'm sorry, pal.
Got to be about the worst birthday ever.
Please don't be mad at me.
Thanks anyway.
Keep the change.
Officer, I can't thank you enough.
So kind, really. Can I pay you back?
Oh, no, My treat.
It just...
You know, it burns me up to see folks
with such backward attitudes toward foxes.
I just wanna say
you're a great dad and just a...
a real articulate fella.
Well, that is high praise. It's rare that
I find someone so non-patronizing.
Officer...
Hopps. Mister...
Wilde. Nick Wilde.
And you, little guy...
You want to be an elephant
when you grow up? You be an elephant.
Because this is Zootopia.
Anyone can be anything.
Boy, I tell him that all the time.
All right, here you go. Two paws. Yeah.
Look at that smile.
That's a "happy birthday" smile.
All right, give her a little
bye-bye toot-toot.
Toot-toot!
Bye, now.
Good bye!
Hey, little Toot-Toot...
Popsicles!
Get your popsicles!
Lumber delivery.
What's with the color?
The color?
That's red wood.
39, 40. There you go.
Way to work that diaper, big guy.
Hey, no kiss bye-bye for daddy?
You kiss me tomorrow,
I'll bite your face off.
Ciao.
Well. I stood up for you,
and you lied to me.
You liar!
It's called a hustle, sweetheart.
And I'm not the liar. He is.
Hey!
All right, slick Nick, you're under arrest.
Really? For what?
Gee, I don't know.
How about selling food without a permit.
Transporting undeclared commerce
across borough lines.
False advertising.
Permit. Receipt of declared commerce.
And I didn't falsely advertise anything.
Take care.
You told that mouse
the Popsicle sticks were redwood!
That's right. "Red wood."
With a space in the middle.
Wood that is red.
You can't touch me, Carrots.
I've been doing this since I was born.
You're gonna want to refrain
from calling me Carrots.
My bad. I just naturally assumed
you came from some little
carrot-choked Podunk, no?
No!
Podunk is in Deerbrooke County,
and I grew up in Bunnyburrow.
Okay. Tell me
if this story sounds familiar.
Naive little hick with good grades
and big ideas...
decides, "Hey, look at me!
I'm gonna move to Zootopia...
where predators and prey
live in harmony and sing "Kumbaya."
Only to find, whoopsie...
we don't all get along. And that
dream of becoming a big city cop?
Double whoopsie. She's a meter maid.
And, whoopsie number three-sie...
no one cares about her or her dreams.
And soon enough, those dreams die
and our bunny sinks into emotional
and literal squalor...
living in a box under a bridge...
till finally she has no choice
but to go back home...
with that cute, fuzzy-wuzzy little tail
between her legs...
to become...
You're from Bunnyburrow,
is that what you said?
So how about a carrot farmer.
That sound about right?
Be careful, now, or it won't just
be your dreams getting crushed.
Hey! No one tells me
what I can or can't be!
Especially not some jerk...
who never had the guts to try to be
anything more than a Popsicle hustler.
All right, look.
Everyone comes to Zootopia...
thinking they can be anything they want.
Well, you can't.
You can only be what you are.
Sly fox, dumb bunny.
I'm not a dumb bunny.
Right. And that's not wet cement.
You'll never be a real cop.
You're a cute meter maid, though.
Maybe a supervisor one day.
Hang in there.
You can't do nothing right, babe
I'm a loser
Oh, hey, it's my parents.
Oh, there she is!
Hi, sweetheart!
Hey there, Jude the dude.
How was your first day on the force?
- It was real great.
- Yeah?
Everything you ever hoped?
Absolutely.
And more. Everyone's so nice and...
- I feel like I'm making a difference.
- Wait a second.
Holy cripes, Bonnie, look at that.
Oh, my sweet heaven!
Judy, are you a meter maid?
This? No! Oh, no.
This is just a temporary thing.
It's the safest job on the force!
She's not a real cop.
Our prayers have been answered!
- Glorious day!
- Meter maid! Meter maid!
- Dad.Dad.Dad!
It's been a really long clay.
I should really...
That's right, you get some rest.
Those meters aren't gonna maid themselves.
Bye-bye.
Buh-bye.
Hey, buddy, turn down that depressing music.
Leave the meter maid alone.
Didn't you hear her conversation?
She feels like a failure!
- Oh, shut up!
- You shut up!
Tomorrow's another day.
Yeah, but it might be worse!
I was 30 seconds over!
You're a real hero, lady!
My mommy says she wishes you were dead.
Uncool, rabbit.
My tax dollars pay your salary.
I am a real cop. I am a real cop.
I am a real cop.
Hey, hey! You, bunny!
Sir. If you have a grievance, you may
contest your citation in traffic court.
What are you talking about?
My shop!
It was just robbed! Look!
He's getting away!
Are you a cop or not?
Yes! Don't worry, sir!
I've got this!
Stop! Stop, in the name of the law!
Catch me if you can, Cottontail!
Coming through!
This is Officer McHorn, we got a 10-31.
I got dibs!
Officer Hopps. I am in pursuit!
You!
Freeze!
Hey, meter maid! Wait for the real cops!
Stop!
Sorry. Coming through.
Excuse me. Excuse me. Pardon.
Bon voyage-e, flat foot!
Hey, stop right there!
Have a donut, copper!
Oh, my God. Did you see
those leopard print jeggings?
I love your hair.
Thank you.
Come to papa.
You're gonna have to be patient and
wait in line just like everyone else...
Mrs. Otterton. Okay?
I popped the weasel!
Hopps!
Abandoning your post.
Inciting a scurry.
Reckless endangerment of rodents.
But, to be fair...
you did stop a master criminal
from stealing two dozen moldy onions.
Hate to disagree with you, sir,
but those aren't onions.
Those are a crocus varietal
called midnicampum holicithias.
They're a Class-C botanical, sir.
I grew up in a family where
plant husbandry was kind of a thing.
Shut your tiny mouth now!
Sir, I got the bad guy.
That's my job.
Your job is putting tickets on parked cars!
Chief, Mrs. Otterton's here
to see you again.
Not now.
Okay, I just didn't know
if you'd want to take it this time.
She seems really upset.
- Not now!
- Sir...
I don't want to be a meter maid,
I want to be a real cop.
Do you think the mayor asked me what
I wanted when he assigned you to me?
But, sir, if...
Life isn't some cartoon musical
where you sing a little song...
and your insipid dreams magically come true.
So, let it go.
Chief Bogo, please.
Five minutes of your time.
I'm sorry, sir.
I tried to stop her.
She is super-slippery.
I gotta go sit down.
Ma'am, as I've told you,
we're doing everything we can.
My husband has been missing for
10 days. His name is Emmitt Otterton.
Yes, I know.
He's a florist.
We have two beautiful children.
He would never just disappear.
Ma'am, our detectives are very busy.
Please. There's got to be someone
to find my Emmitt.
Mrs. Otterton...
I will find him.
Thank you.
Bless you. Bless you, little bunny.
Take this.
Find my Emmitt. Bring him home...
to me and my babies, please.
Mrs. Otterton, please wait out here.
Of course. Thank you both so much.
One second.
You're fired.
What? Why?
Insubordination!
Now. I'm going to open this door...
and you're going to tell that otter
you're a former meter maid...
with delusions of grandeur...
who will not be taking the case!
I just heard Officer Hopps is taking the case.
Assistant Mayor Bellwether.
The Mammal Inclusion Initiative
is really starting to pay off.
Mayor Lionheart is just gonna be so jazzed!
No, let's not tell the Mayor just yet.
And I've sent it and it is done,
so I did do that.
Well, I'd say the case is in good hands.
Us little guys really need to
stick together, right?
Like glue.
Good one.
Just call me if you ever need anything, okay?
You've always got a friend at City Hall, Judy.
All right, bye-bye.
Thank you, ma'am.
I will give you 48 hours.
Yes!
That's two days to find Emmitt Otterton.
Okay.
But, you strike out, you resign.
Deal!
Splendid. Clawhauser will
give you the complete case file.
Here you go.
One missing otter.
That's it?
Yikes! That is the smallest case file
I've ever seen.
Leads, none. Witnesses, none.
And you're not in the computer system
yet, so resources, none!
I hope you didn't stake your career
on cracking this one!
Okay. Last known sighting.
Can I just borrow...
Thank you.
Popsicle?
The murder weapon.
Get your Popsicle.
Yeah. Because that...
What does that mean?
It means...
I have a lead.
Hi! Hello? It's me, again!
Hey, it's Officer Toot-Toot.
No. Actually, it's Officer Hopps...
and I'm here to ask you some questions
about a case.
What happened, meter maid?
Did someone steal a traffic cone?
It wasn't me.
Hey, Carrots, you're going to
wake the baby. I gotta get to work.
This is important, sir.
I think your $10 worth of popsicles can wait.
I make 200 bucks a day, Fluff!
365 days a year, since I was 12.
And time is money. Hop along.
Please, just look at the picture.
You sold Mr. Otterton that Popsicle,
right? Do you know him?
I know everybody.
And I also know that, somewhere...
there's a toy store
missing its stuffed animal,
so why don't you get back to your box?
Fine. Then we'll have to do this
the hard way.
Did you just boot my stroller?
Nicholas Wilde, you are under arrest.
For what? Hurting your feelings?
Felony Tax Evasion.
Yeah, $200 a day, 365 days a year,
since you were 12.
That's two decades, so times 20,
which is $1,460,000, I think.
I mean,I am just a dumb bunny,
but we are good at multiplying.
Anyway, according to your tax forms...
you reported, let me see here... zero!
Unfortunately, lying on a federal form
is a punishable offense.
Five years jail time.
Well, it's my word against yours.
200 bucks a day, Fluff!
365 days a year, since I was 12.
Actually, it's your word against yours.
And if you want this pen, you're going to
help me find this poor, missing otter...
or the only place you'll be selling
popsicles is the prison cafeteria.
It's called a hustle, sweetheart.
She hustled you.
She hustled you good!
You a cop now, Nick.
You gonna need one of these.
Have fun...
working with the fuzz!
Start talking.
I don't know where he is.
I only saw where he went.
Great. Let's go.
It's not exactly a place for...
a cute little bunny.
Don't call me cute. Get in the car.
Okay. You're the boss.
Hi.
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Hello. My name is...
You know, I'm going to hit
the pause button right there...
because we're all good on Bunny Scout cookies.
No.
I'm Officer Hopps, ZPD.
I'm looking for a missing mammal,
Emmitt Otterton, right here...
who may have frequented this establishment.
Yeah, old Emmitt.
Haven't seen him in a couple of weeks.
But, hey, you should talk
to his yoga instructor.
I'd be happy to take you back.
Thank you so much.
I'd appreciate that more than
you can imagine, it would be such...
You are naked!
For sure, we're a naturalist club.
Yeah. In Zootopia,
anyone can be anything.
These guys, they be naked.
Nangi's just on the other side
of the Pleasure Pool.
Oh, boy.
Does this make you uncomfortable?
Because if so, there is no
shame in calling it quits.
Yes, there is.
Boy, that's the spirit.
Yeah, some mammals say
the naturalist life is weird...
but you know what I say is weird?
Clothes on animals!
Here we go.
As you can see, Nangi's an elephant,
so she'll totally remember everything.
Hey, Nangi.
These dudes have some questions
about Emmitt the otter.
Who?
Emmitt Otterton? Been coming to
your yoga class for like...
6 years?
I have no memory of this beaver.
He's an otter, actually.
He was here a couple Wednesdays ago, remember?
No.
Yeah, he was wearing
a green cable-knit sweater vest...
and a new pair of corduroy slacks.
And a paisley tie, sweet Windsor knot.
Real tight. Remember that, Nangi?
No.
And we both walked him out,
and he got into this big old white car
with a silver trim.
Needed a tune-up.
The third cylinder wasn't firing.
- Remember that, Nangi?
- No.
You didn't happen to catch
the license plate number, did you?
Oh, for sure. It was 2-9...
T-H-D...
- 0-3.
- 0-3. Wow.
This is a lot of great info. Thank you.
Told you Nangi has a mind like a steel trap.
I wish I had a memory like an elephant.
Well, I had a ball.
You are welcome for the clue...
and seeing as how any moron can run a plate,
I will take that pen and bid you adieu.
The plate. I can't run a plate.
I'm not in the system yet.
Give me the pen, please.
What was it you said?
"Any moron can run a plate"?
Gosh. If only there were a moron around
who were up to the task.
Rabbit, I did what you asked!
You can't keep me on the hook forever.
Not forever. Well, I only have
36 hours left to solve this case.
So can you run the plate or not?
Actually, I just remembered...
I have a pal at the DMV.
Flash is the fastest guy in there.
If you need something done, he's on it.
I hope so. We are really fighting
the clock and every minute counts.
Wait. They're all sloths?
You said this was going to be quick!
Are you saying that because
he's a sloth, he can't be fast?
I thought in Zootopia,
anyone could be anything.
Flash, Flash, hundred-yard dash.
Buddy, it's nice to see you.
Nice to...
see you...
too.
Hey, Flash, I'd love you to meet my friend.
Darling, I've forgotten your name.
Officer Judy Hopps, ZPD, how are you?
I am...
doing...
just...
Fine?
...as well as...
I can...
be.
- What...
- Hang in there.
...can I...
- ...do...
- I was hoping you could run a...
...for you...
Well, I was hoping you could...
...today?
Well, I was hoping you could
run a plate for us.
We are in a really big hurry.
Sure.
What's the...
- plate...
- 2-9-T...
...number?
2-9-T-H-D-0-3
Two...
nine...
T-H-D-0-3.
...T...
H-D-0-3.
...H...
D-0-3.
...D...
0-3.
...0...
3.
Hey, Flash, want to hear a joke?
No!
Sure.
Okay. What do you call
a three-humped camel?
I don't...
know.
What...
do...
you call...
- a...
- Three-humped camel.
...three-humped...
camel?
Pregnant.
Yes, very funny, very funny.
Can we please just focus on the...
- Hey...
- Wait, wait, wait!
...Priscilla!
Oh, no!
Yes...
Flash?
What...
do...
- No!
- ...you call a...
A three-humped camel? "Pregnant!"
Okay, great, we got it.
...three... humped...
- Here...
- Yeah. Hurry.
- ...you...
- Thank you. "2-9-T-H-D-O-3."
...go.
It's registered to Tundratown Limo Service.
A limo took Otterton,
and the limo's in Tundratown!
Way to hustle, bud.
I love you. I owe you.
Hurry! We gotta beat
the rush hour, and...
It's night?
Closed. Great.
And I will bet you
you don't have a warrant to get in.
Darn it. It's a bummer.
You wasted the day on purpose.
Madam, I have a fake badge.
I would never impede
your pretend investigation.
It's not a pretend investigation. Look,
see? See him? This otter is missing.
Then they should've gotten
a real cop to find him.
What is your problem?
Does seeing me fail
somehow make you feel better
about your own sad, miserable life?
It does. 100%.
Now, since you're sans warrant...
I guess we're... done?
Fine. We are done.
Here's your pen.
Hey!
First off, you throw like a bunny.
Second, you're a very sore loser.
See you later, Officer Fluff.
So sad this is over.
I wish I could've helped more.
The thing is, you don't need a warrant
if you have probable cause...
and I'm pretty sure I saw
a shifty lowlife climbing the fence.
So you're helping plenty. Come on.
2-9-T-H-D-0-3.
This is it!
Polar bear fur.
- Oh, my God!
- What?
The Velvety Pipes of Jerry Vole.
But on CD.
Who still uses CDs?
Carrots, if your otter was here,
he had a very bad day.
Those are claw marks.
You ever seen anything like this?
No.
Wait, look.
This is him, Emmitt Otterton.
He was definitely here.
What do you think happened?
Now, wait a minute.
Polar bear fur, Rat Pack music, fancy cup?
I know whose car this is. We got to go.
Why? Whose car is it?
The most feared crime-boss
in Tundratown. They call him Mr. Big.
And he does not like me.
So we gotta go!
I'm not leaving.
This is a crime scene.
It's gonna be an even bigger
crime scene if Mr. Big finds me here...
so we're leaving right now.
Raymond!
And is that Kevin?
Long time, no see.
And, speaking of "no see,"
how about you forget you saw me?
For old times' sake?
That's a no.
What did you do that made
Mr. Big so mad at you?
I may have sold him
a very expensive wool rug...
that was made from the fur of a skunk...
...'s butt.
Sweet cheese and crackers.
Is that Mr. Big?
No.
What about him?
- Is that him?
- No!
That's got to be him.
Stop talking, stop talking, stop talking!
Mr. Big, sir. This is a simple...
Yeah.
This is a simple misunderstanding.
You come here, unannounced, on the
day my daughter is to be married.
Well, actually, we were brought here
against our will, so...
The point is, I did not know
that it was your car...
and I certainly did not know
about your daughter's wedding.
I trusted you, Nicky.
I welcomed you into my home.
We broke bread together.
Gram-mama made you a cannoli.
And how did you repay my generosity?
With a rug made from the butt of a skunk.
A skunk-butt rug.
You disrespected me.
You disrespected my Gram-mama,
who I buried in that skunk butt rug.
I told you never to show your face
here again but here you are...
snooping around with this...
What are you? A performer?
What's with the costume?
Sir. I am a...
Mime! She is a mime.
This... mime cannot speak.
You can't speak if you're a mime.
No, I am a cop.
And I'm on the Emmitt Otterton case.
And my evidence puts him in your car.
So intimidate me all you want.
I'm going to find out what you did
to that otter if it's the last thing I do.
Then I have only one request.
Say hello to Gram-mama.
Ice 'em.
I didn't see nothing!
I'm not saying nothing!
And you never will.
Please! No, no, no!
If you're mad at me about the rug,
I've got more rugs!
Daddy! It's time for our dance!
What did we say?
No icing anyone at my wedding!
I have to, baby. Daddy has to.
Ice 'em.
No, no no!
Wait. Please!
She's the bunny that saved my life yesterday!
From that giant donut.
This bunny?
Yeah! Hi!
Hi. I love your dress.
Thank you.
Put 'em down.
You've done me a great service.
I will help you find the otter.
I will take your kindness and pay it forward.
Otterton is my florist.
He's like a part of the family.
He had something important
he wanted to discuss.
That's why I sent that car to pick him up.
But he never arrived.
Because he was attacked.
No. He attacked.
Otterton?
Otterton. He went crazy.
Ripped up the car,
scared my driver half to death...
and disappeared into the night.
But he's a sweet little otter.
My child, we may be evolved, but deep down...
we are still animals.
You want to find Otterton,
talk to the driver of that car.
His name is Manchas...
lives in the Rainforest District.
Only he can tell you more.
Mr. Manchas?
Judy Hopps, ZPD.
We just wanna know
what happened to Emmitt Otterton.
You...
should be asking...
what happened to me.
A teensy otter did that?
What happened?
He was an animal.
Down...
on all fours.
He was a savage!
There was no warning.
He just kept yelling about the Night Howlers.
Over and over. The Night Howlers.
So you know about the Night Howlers, too?
Good. Good, good.
Because the Night Howlers are exactly
what we are here to talk about.
Right?
- Yup.
So, you just open the door...
and tell us what you know...
and we will tell you
what we know. Okay?
Okay.
Clever fox.
Mr. Manchas?
Buddy?
Are you...
okay?
Run. Run!
What is wrong with him?
I don't know!
Jump!
Come on!
Head down!
Officer Hopps to Dispatch.
Are you familiar with Gazelle, greatest
singer of our lifetime, angel with horns?
Okay, hold on. Keep watching.
Who's that beside her? Who is it?
Wow, you are one hot dancer,
Benjamin Clawhauser.
It's me! Did you think it was real?
It looks so real!
It's not, it's just a new app.
Hold on a second.
Clawhauser!
Listen to me, we have a 10-91!
Jaguar gone savage!
Vine and Tuh-junja!
It's "Tuh-hunga!"
Okay, we 're sending backup! Hopps?
Hopps!
There!
Head for the sky trams!
Get in! Carrots.
Carrots!
Go!
No, no, no!
Buddy.
One predator to another...
Now, I can tell you're a little tense...
so I'm just gonna give you
a little personal space!
Rabbit, whatever you do, do not let go!
- I'm gonna let go!
- No, you, what?
One, two...
Carrots. You saved my life.
Well. That's what we do at the ZPD.
Well, this should be good.
I thought this was
just a missing mammal case...
but it's way bigger.
Mr. Otterton did not just disappear.
I believe he and this jaguar,
they went savage, sir.
Savage? This isn't the Stone Age,
Hopps. Animals don't "go savage."
I thought so, too, until I saw this.
What? He was right here.
The "savage" jaguar?
Sir, I know what I saw.
He almost killed us!
Or, maybe any aggressive predator
looks savage to you rabbits.
Let's go!
Wait, sir.
I'm not the only one who saw him.
Nick!
You think I'm gonna believe a fox?
He was a key witness, and I...
Two days to find the otter...
or you quit.
That was the deal.
Badge.
- But, sir, we...
- Badge!
No.
What did you say, fox?
Sorry. What I said was, "no."
She will not be giving you that badge.
Look, you give her a clown vest
and a three-wheeled joke-mobile...
and two days to solve a case
you guys haven't cracked in two weeks?
Yeah.
No wonder she needed to get help from a fox.
None of you guys
were gonna help her, were you?
Here's the thing, Chief.
You gave her the 48 hours...
so, technically, we still have...
10 left to find our Mr. Otterton...
and that is exactly what we're gonna do.
So, if you'll excuse us, we have a very
big lead to follow and a case to crack.
Good day.
Officer Hopps.
Thank you.
Never let them see that they get to you.
So...
things do get to you?
No, I mean, not anymore...
but I was small and emotionally
unbalanced like you once.
Har-har..
No, it's true.
I think I was 8, or maybe 9...
and all I wanted to do
was join the Junior Ranger Scouts.
So, my mom scraped together enough money
to buy me a brand-new uniform...
because, by God, I was gonna fit in.
Even if I was the only predator in the troop.
The only fox.
Okay, Nick.
I was gonna be pan' of a pack.
Ready for initiation?
Yeah. Pretty much born ready.
I was so proud.
Okay.
Now, raise your right paw
and deliver the oath.
I, Nicholas Wilde, promise to be brave...
loyal, helpful, and trustworthy.
Even though you're a fox?
What?
No! What did I do wrong, you guys?
No, please! Tell me!
What did I do wrong?
What did I do?
If you thought we would ever
trust a fox without a muzzle...
you're even dumber than you look!
Aw, is he gonna cry?
I learned two things that day.
One...
I was never gonna let anyone see
that they got to me.
And two?
If the world's only gonna see a fox
as shifty and untrustworthy...
there's no point in trying
to be anything else.
Nick, you are so much more than that.
Boy, look at that traffic down there.
How about we go out to Chuck
in Traffic Central.
Chuck, how are things looking on the Jam Cams?
Nick, I'm glad you told me.
The Jam Cams.
- Seriously. It's okay.
- No, no, no.
There are traffic cameras everywhere!
All over the canopy!
Whatever happened to that jaguar...
The traffic cams would have caught it!
Bingo!
Pretty sneaky, slick!
However, if you didn't have access
to the system before...
I doubt Chief Buffalo Butt
is gonna let you into it now.
No.
But I have a friend at City Hall who might.
Sir, if we could just review
these very important...
Sir...
I'm so sorry. Sir!
Okay. I heard you, Bellwether.
Just take care of it.
Please. And clear my afternoon.
I'm going out.
No, no! But, sir, you do have a meeting
with Herds and Grazing.
Sir, if I could just...
Oh, mutton chops.
Assistant Mayor Bellwether?
We need your help.
We just need to get into
the traffic cam database.
So fluffy!
Hey!
Sheep never let me get this close.
You can't just touch a sheep's wool!
It's like cotton candy.
Stop it!
Where to?
Rainforest District, Vine and Tujunga.
There! Traffic cams for the whole city.
This is so exciting, actually!
I never get to do anything this important.
But you're the Assistant Mayor of Zootopia.
I'm more of a glorified secretary.
I think Mayor Lionheart
just wanted the sheep vote.
But he did give me that nice mug.
Feels good to be appreciated.
Smell-wether!
That's a fun little name he likes to use.
I called him Lion-fart once.
He did not care for that. Let me tell you,
it was not a good day for me.
Yes, sir?
I thought you were going to
cancel my afternoon!
Oh, dear. I better go.
Let me know what you find.
It was really nice for me to be...
While we 're young, Smell-wether!
You think when she goes to sleep
she counts herself?
Shush. Okay, traffic cams.
Tujunga, Tujunga... We're in.
Who are these guys?
Timberwolves.
Look at these dumb-dumbs.
Bet you a nickel one of them is gonna howl.
And there it is.
What is it with wolves and the howling?
It's like...
Howlers. Night Howlers.
That's what Manchas was afraid of!
Wolves!
The wolves are the Night Howlers.
If they took Manchas...
I'll bet they took Otterton, too.
All we gotta do is find out where they went.
Wait, where did they go?
If I wanted to avoid surveillance
because I was doing something illegal...
which I never have...
I would use the maintenance tunnel 6B.
Which would put them out...
right there.
Well, look at you, Junior Detective.
You know, I think you'd actually
make a pretty good cop.
How dare you.
Acacia Alley?
Ficus Underpass.
South Canyon.
They're heading out of town.
Where does that road go?
Gary, quit it!
You're gonna start a howl.
I didn't start it!
Come on.
You are a clever bunny.
It looks like this was a hospital.
You know, after you.
You're the cop.
Okay, all clear.
All this equipment is brand new.
Carrots.
Claw marks.
Yeah, huge claw marks.
What kind of...
Mr. Manchas.
It's him.
We found our otter.
Mr. Otterton.
My name is Officer Judy Hopps.
Your wife sent me to find you.
We're gonna get you out of here now.
Or not.
Guess he's in no rush
to get home to the missus.
11,12,13,14...
Not including Manchas, it's 14.
Chief Bogo handed out 14 missing mammal files.
They're all here.
All the missing mammals are right here.
Enough! I don't want excuses, Doctor!
I want answers.
Mayor Lionheart, please.
We're doing everything we can.
Really?
Because I got a dozen and a half animals here
who have gone off-the-rails crazy...
and you can't tell me why.
Now, I'd call that awfully far
from "doing everything."
Sir...
it may be time to consider their biology.
What? What do you mean "biology?"
The only animals going savage are predators.
We cannot keep it a secret.
We need to come forward.
Great idea. Tell the public.
And how do you think they're gonna feel
about their mayor...
who is a lion?
I'll be ruined!
Well, what does Chief Bogo say?
Chief Bogo doesn't know.
And we are going to keep it that way.
No, no, no!
Someone's here.
Sir, you need to go, now!
Security! Sweep the area!
Great! We're dead. We're dead.
That's it. I'm dead, you're dead.
Everybody's dead!
Can you swim?
What? Can I swim?
Yes, I can swim. Why?
Carrots! Hopps! Judy!
We gotta tell Bogo!
Wow! You are one hot dancer,
Chief Bogo.
- Chief Bogo!
- Not now!
Wait, is that Gazelle?
No.
I'm Gazelle, and you are one hot dancer.
You have the app too?
Chief!
Clawhauser, can't you see I'm working
on the missing mammal cases?
Yes of course! About that, sir.
Officer Hopps just called.
She found all of them.
Wow! I'm impressed.
Mayor Lionheart, you have the right
to remain silent. Anything...
You don't understand.
I was trying to protect the city!
You were just trying to protect your job.
No. Listen, we still don't know
why this is happening.
It could destroy Zootopia.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will
be used against you in a court of law.
Ladies and gentlemammals.
14 mammals went missing...
and all 14 have been found
by our newest recruit...
who will speak to you in a moment.
But first, let me remind you...
I'm so nervous.
Okay. Press Conference 101.
You wanna look smart? Answer
their question with your own question...
and then answer
that question. Like this.
"Excuse me. Officer Hopps,
what can you tell us about the case?"
"Well, was this a tough case?
"Yes. Yes, it was."
You see?
You should be there with me.
We did this together.
Well, am I a cop?
No. No, I am not.
Funny you should say that,
because I've been thinking...
It would be nice to have a partner.
Here. In case
you need something to write with.
At twenty-two hundred hours,
we found all these missing animals...
Officer Hopps, it's time.
They appear to be in good health,
physically, if not emotionally.
So now, I'll turn things over
to the officer who cracked the case.
Officer Judy Hopps.
- Officer Hopps!
Over here!
Yes?
What can you tell us about
the animals that went savage?
Well, the animals in question...
Are they all different species?
Yes. Yes, they are.
Okay, so what is the connection?
All we know is that they are all
members of the predator family.
So, predators are the only ones going savage?
That is accurate. Yes.
Why is this happening?
We still don't know.
It may have something to do with biology.
What do you mean by that?
A biological component.
You know, something in their DNA.
In their DNA?
Can you elaborate on that, please?
Yes, what I mean is, thousands of years ago...
predators survived through their aggressive...
hunting instincts.
For whatever reason...
they seem to be reverting back
to their primitive, savage ways.
Of course they did.
Aw, is he gonna cry?
Officer Hopps, could it happen again?
It is possible.
So we must be vigilant.
And we at the ZPD are prepared
and are here to protect you.
Will more mammals go savage?
What is being done to protect us?
Have you considered a mandatory
quarantine on predators?
Okay, thank you, Officer Hopps.
That's all the time that we have.
No more questions.
Was I okay?
You did fine.
That went so fast.
I didn't get a chance to mention you,
or say anything about how we...
I think you said plenty.
What do you mean?
"Clearly there's
a biological component?"
"These predators may be reverting back
to their primitive, savage ways?"
Are you serious?
I just stated the facts of the case.
I mean it's not like a bunny could go savage.
Right. But a fox could?
Nick, stop it.
You're not like them.
Oh, there's a "them" now?
You know what I mean.
You're not that kind of predator.
The kind that needs to be muzzled?
The kind that makes you think
you need to carry around fox repellent?
Yeah, don't think I didn't notice
that little item the first time we met.
So let me ask you a question.
Are you afraid of me?
Do you think I might go nuts?
Do you think I might go savage?
Do you think I might try to...
eat you?
I knew it.
Just when I thought somebody
actually believed in me.
Probably best if you don't have
a predator as a partner.
No. Nick. Nick!
Officer Hopps! Were you just
threatened by that predator?
No, he's my friend.
We can't even trust our own friends?
That is not what I said! Please!
Are we safe?
Have any foxes gone savage?
More bad news in this city gripped by fear.
A caribou is in critical condition,
the victim of a mauling...
by a savage polar bear.
This, the 27th such attack,
comes just one week...
after ZPD Officer Judy Hopps
connected the violence
to traditionally predatory animals.
Meanwhile, a peace rally
organized by pop star Gazelle...
was marred by protest.
Go back to the forest, predator!
I'm from the savanna!
Zootopia is a unique place.
It's a crazy, beautiful, diverse city...
where we celebrate our differences.
This is not the Zootopia I know.
The Zootopia I know is better than this.
We don't just blindly assign blame.
We don't know why these attacks
keep happening...
but it is irresponsible
to label all predators as savages.
That's not my Emmitt.
We cannot let fear divide us.
Please give me back the Zootopia I love.
Come on, Hopps.
The new mayor wants to see us.
The mayor? Why?
It would seem you've arrived.
Clawhauser?
What are you doing?
They thought it would be better...
if a predator such as myself
wasn't the first face that you see...
when you walk into the ZPD.
What?
They're gonna move me to records.
It's downstairs.
It's by the boiler.
Hopps!
I don't understand.
Our city is 90% prey, Judy...
and right now they're just really scared.
You're a hero to them.
They trust you.
And so that's why Chief Bogo and I want
you to be the public face of the ZPD.
I'm not a hero.
I came here
to make the world a better place...
but I think I broke it.
Don't give yourself so much credit, Hopps.
The world has always been broken,
that's why we need good cops.
Like you.
With all due respect, sir, a good cop...
is supposed to serve and protect.
Help the city.
Not tear it apart.
I don't deserve this badge.
Hopps...
Judy, you've worked so hard to get here.
It's what you wanted since you were a kid.
You can't quit.
Thank you for the opportunity.
A dozen carrots.
- Thanks.
- Have a nice day.
Come on.
Hey, there, Jude.
Jude the dude.
Remember that one?
How we doing?
I'm fine.
You are not fine.
Your ears are droopy.
Why did I think I could make a difference?
Because you're a trier, that's why.
You've always been a trier.
Oh, I tried.
And it made life so much
worse for so many innocent predators.
Not all of them, though.
Speak of the devil.
Right on time.
Is that Gideon Grey?
Yep. It sure is.
We work with him now.
He's our partner.
And we would never have considered it
had you not opened our minds.
That's right.
Gid's turned into one of the
top pastry chefs in the tri-burrows.
That's really cool, you guys.
Gideon Grey.
I'll be darned.
Hey, Judy. I'd just like to say I'm sorry
for the way I behaved in my youth.
I had a lot of self-doubt,
and it manifested itself in the form
of unchecked rage and aggression.
I was a major jerk.
I know a thing or two about being a jerk.
Anyhow, I brought y'all these pies.
Hey, kids, don't you run through
that midnicampum holicithias.
Well, now, there's a $4 word, Mr. H.
My family always
just called them Night Howlers.
What did you say?
Gid's talking about those flowers, Judy.
I use them to keep the bugs off the produce...
but I don't like the little ones
going near 'em...
on account of what happened
to your uncle Terry.
Yeah, Terry ate one whole when we were kids
and went completely nuts.
He bit the dickens out of your mother.
A bunny can go savage.
Savage? Well, that's a strong word.
But it did hurt like the devil.
Sure it did! There's a sizable divot
in your arm. I'd call that savage.
Night Howlers aren't wolves, they're flowers!
The flowers are making
the predators go savage!
That's it! That's what I've been missing!
Keys!
Keys, keys, keys!
Hurry! Come on!
Thank you! I love you! Bye!
You catch any of that, Bon?
Not one bit.
That makes me feel a little bit better.
I thought she was talking in tongues.
Who is it?
I need to find Nick.
Please.
Nick?
Nick!
Oh, Nick.
Night Howlers aren't wolves.
They're toxic flowers.
I think someone
is targeting predators on purpose
and making them go savage!
Wow.
Isn't that interesting?
Wait! I know you'll never forgive me!
And I don't blame you.
I wouldn't forgive me either.
I was ignorant...
And irresponsible and small-minded.
But predators shouldn't have
to suffer for my mistakes.
I have to fix this.
But I can't do it without you.
And after we're done...
you can hate me.
And that'll be fine.
Because I was a horrible friend...
and I hurt you.
And you can walk away knowing
that you were right all along.
I really am just a dumb bunny.
Don't worry, Carrots.
I'll let you erase it...
in 48 hours.
All right. Get in here.
Okay. You bunnies are so emotional.
There we go. Deep breath.
Are you just trying to steal the pen?
Is that what this is?
You are standing on my tail, though.
Off, off, off.
I'm sorry.
I thought you guys only grew carrots.
What's the plan?
We are gonna follow the Night Howlers.
Okay. How?
Know this guy?
I told you. I know everybody.
Step right up.
Anything you need, I got it.
All your favorite movies!
I got movies that
haven't even been released yet.
Hey, 15% off! 20!
Make me an offer! Come on!
Well, well, look who it is.
The duke of bootleg.
What's it to you, Wilde?
Shouldn't you be melting down
a Popsicle or something?
Hey, if it ain't Flopsy the Copsy.
We both know those weren't
moldy onions I caught you stealing.
What were you gonna do
with those Night Howlers, Wezzleton?
It's Weaselton! Duke Weaselton!
And I ain't talking, rabbit.
And there ain't nothing you can do to make me.
Ice him.
You dirty rat! Why are you helping her?
She's a cop!
And the godmother to my future granddaughter.
I'm gonna name her Judy.
Ice this weasel.
All right, all right, please!
I'll talk! I'll talk.
I stole them Night Howlers
so I could sell 'em.
They offered me what I couldn't refuse.
Money.
And to whom did you sell them?
A ram named Doug.
We got a drop spot underground.
Just watch it.
Doug is the opposite of friendly.
He's unfriendly.
Come on.
The weasel wasn't lying.
Yeah, looks like old Doug's cornered
the market on Night Howlers.
You got Doug here.
What's the mark?
Cheetah in Sahara Square. Got it.
Serious? Yeah, I know they're fast.
I can hit him.
Listen, I hit a tiny little otter through
the open window of a moving car.
Yeah, I'll buzz you when it's done.
Or you'll see it on the news.
You know, whichever comes first.
Hey, Doug, open up!
We've got your latte.
Woolter and Jesse are back,
so I'm leaving now.
Out.
Where are you going?
Get back here!
What are you doing?
He's gonna see you!
What are you looking at? Hey!
Whatever you're thinking,
stop thinking it. Carrots!
Carrots!
It better have the extra foam this time.
Hey, open UP!
What are you doing?
You just trapped us in here.
We need to get this evidence to the ZPD!
Great! Here it is. Got it!
- No. All of it!
- Wait, what?
Great, you're a conductor now?
It would take a miracle
to get this rust-bucket going.
Well. Hallelujah.
We kinda got a situation at the lab.
It just got worse!
Mission accomplished.
Would it be premature
for me to do a little victory toot-toot?
All right. One toot-toot.
Well, I can cross that off the bucket list.
I may have to rescind that victory
toot-toot.
Maybe that's just hail.
Come here!
Back off!
Incoming!
Carrots!
Don't stop! Keep going!
No, no! Please stop!
Do not stop this car!
Speed up, Nick! Speed up!
There's another train coming!
Trust me. Speed up!
Stop the train!
Hey!
Need some help?
Oh, no, no, no! Too fast!
Hold on!
I think this is our stop!
Maybe some of the evidence survived.
Everything is gone.
We've lost it all.
Yeah...
except for this.
Nick! Yes!
Come on! We gotta get to the ZPD.
Cut through the Natural History Museum!
There it is!
Judy!
Mayor Bellwether!
We found out what's happening.
Someone's darting predators with a serum.
That's what's making them go savage.
I'm so proud of you, Judy.
You did just a super job!
Thank you, ma'am.
How did you know where to find us?
I'll go ahead and I'll take that case now.
You know what? I think Nick and I
will just take this to the ZPD.
Run.
Get them.
Carrots!
I got you! Come here, come here.
Okay, now just relax.
Blueberry?
Pass.
Come on out, Judy.
Take the case.
Get it to Bogo.
I'm not gonna leave you behind.
That's not happening.
I can't walk.
We'll think of something.
We're on the same team, Judy.
Underestimated, underappreciated.
Aren't you sick of it?
Predators.
They may be strong and loud...
but prey outnumber predators 10 to 1.
Think Of it.
90% of the population...
united against a common enemy.
We'll be unstoppable.
Over there!
Help!
Well, you should have just stayed
on the carrot farm, huh?
It really is too bad. I did like you.
What are you going to do? Kill me?
No, of course not.
He is.
No! Nick!
Yes, police! There's a savage fox
in the Natural History Museum.
Officer Hopps is down! Please, hurry.
No. Nick, don't do this. Fight it.
But he can't help it, can he?
Since preds are just biologically
predisposed to be savages.
Gosh. Think of the headline!
"Hero cop killed by savage fox."
So that's it? Prey fears predator,
and you stay in power?
Yeah, pretty much.
It won't work!
Fear always works.
And I'll dart every predator
in Zootopia to keep it that way.
Oh, Nick.
No.
BYE-bye, bunny.
Blood! Blood! Blood and death.
All right, you're milking it.
Besides, I think we got it.
We got it up there, thank you,
Yakety-yak!
You laid it all out beautifully.
What?
Are you looking for the serum?
Well, it's right here.
What you've got in the weapon there?
Those are blueberries.
From my family's farm.
They are delicious.
You should try some.
I framed Lionheart.
I can frame you, too.
It's my word against yours.
Actually...
And I'll dart every predator in Zootopia
to keep it that way.
...it's your word against yours.
It's called a hustle, sweetheart. Boom.
Former mayor Dawn Bellwether
is behind bars today...
guilty of masterminding the savage attacks
that have plagued Zootopia of late.
Her predecessor, Leodore Lionheart,
denies any knowledge of her plot...
claiming he was just trying
to protect the city.
Did I falsely imprison those animals?
Well, yes. Yes, I did.
It was a classic "doing the wrong thing
for the right reason" kind of a deal.
In related news, doctors say
the Night Howler antidote
is proving effective...
in rehabilitating the afflicted predators.
Emmitt.
Thank you.
When I was a kid...
...l thought Zootopia
was this perfect place.
Where everyone got along
and anyone could be anything.
Turns out, real life's a little bit
more complicated...
than a slogan on a bumper sticker.
Real life is messy.
We all have limitations.
We all make mistakes.
Which means, hey, glass half-full,
we all have a lot in common.
And the more we try
to understand one another...
the more exceptional each of us will be.
But we have to try.
So, no matter what type of animal you are...
from the biggest elephant...
to our first fox...
I implore you... try.
Try to make the world a better place.
Look inside yourself...
and recognize that change...
starts with you.
It starts with me.
It starts with all of us.
All right, enough! Shut it!
We have some new recruits
with us this morning...
including our first fox.
Who cares?
You should have your own line
of inspirational greeting cards, sir.
Shut your mouth, Wilde.
Assignments.
Officers Grizzoli, Fangmeyer, Delgato...
Tundratown SWAT.
Snarlov, Higgins, Wolfard...
undercover.
Hopps, Wilde.
Parking duty.
Dismissed.
Just kidding!
We have reports of a street racer
tearing up Savannah Central.
Find him, shut him down.
So, are all rabbits bad drivers,
or is it just you?
Oops. Sorry.
Sly bunny.
Dumb fox.
You know you love me.
Do I know that?
Yes. Yes, I do.
Sir, you were going 115 miles per hour.
I hope you have a good explanation.
Flash?
Flash? Hundred yard dash?
Nick.
Good evening, Zootopia!
Come on, everybody, put your paws up!
I messed up tonight
I lost another fight
Lost to myself
But I 'll just start again
I keep falling down
I keep on hitting the ground
But I always get up now
To see what's next
I won't give up
No, I won't give in
Till I reach the end
And then I'll start again
No, I won't leave
I want to try everything
I want to try even though I could fail
I won't give up
No, I won't give in
Till I reach the end
Then I'll start again
No, I won't leave
I want to try everything
I want to try even though I could fail
Try everything
Put your paws in the air. Come on!
Look how far you've come
You filled your heart with love
Baby, you've done enough
Take a deep breath
Don't beat yourself up
No need to run so fast
Sometimes we come last
But we did our best
I won't give up
No, I won't give in
Till I reach the end
And then I'll start again
No, I won't leave
I want to try everything
I want to try
Even though I could fail
I won't give up
No, I won't give in
Till I reach the end
Then I'll start again
No, I won't leave
I want to try everything
I want to try even though I could fail
I'll keep on making those new mistakes
And I'll keep on making them every day
Those new mistakes
Try everything
Come on!
Shake your tails with me. Come on!
Yeah!
I'll keep on making those new mistakes
I'll keep on making them every day
Those new mistakes
Try everything